Ted Koppel Collection
Ted Koppel Collection
- Miscellaneous media, 1984-2007
  - Unidentified and miscellaneous items, 1984-2007
    - Life 360
      Holdings for this program include tape dubs in various formats of the following episodes/segments (multiple copies of most): "A Place in Time", "Flying", "Food", "Junk", "Leaving Home", "Milestones", "Money", "Roots", "Six Degrees of Separation", "Voice", and a rough cut "Highlights Reel".
      - A Place in Time (LITH102 K1) (S1-2), 10/08/2001; Videotape, Betacam SP, dub, 56:46:00; koppel_01279 (Box 60)
      - A Place in Time (LITH102 K1) (Dub from Master), 10/08/2001; Videotape, VHS, dub, 56:46:00; koppel_01280 (Box 56)
      - Flying (LITH110 K1), 12/10/2001; Videotape, Betacam SP, dub, 56:46:00; koppel_01306 (Box 77)
      - Flying, 12/10/2001; Videotape, VHS, dub, 56:46:00; koppel_01307 (Box 56)
      - Flying, 12/10/2001; Videotape, VHS, dub, 56:46:00; koppel_01308 (Box 56)
      - Flying, 12/10/2001; Videotape, VHS, dub, 56:46:00; koppel_01309 (Box 56)
      - Dub - 4 Channels (Orig Air: 10/20/2001), 01/30/2003; Videotape, Betacam, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01288 (Box 77)
      - Food (Review Copy) (Incomplete: not for broadcast) (51O) (29-B), 09/09/2001; Videotape, Digital Betacam, dub, 0:44:55; koppel_01289 (Box 77)
      - Dumpster Diving (Segment), 09/06/2001; Videotape, Betacam, dub, 0:09:09; koppel_01290 (Box 64)
      - Dumpster Diving (Segment), 09/06/2001; Videotape, Betacam, dub, 0:09:09; koppel_01291 (Box 64)
      - Dumpster Diving (Segment), 09/06/2001; Videotape, Betacam, dub, 0:09:09; koppel_01292 (Box 64)
      - Cuban Food (Segment), 09/2001; Videotape, Betacam SP, dub, 0:08:05; koppel_01293 (Box 64)
      - Cuban Food (Segment), 09/2001; Videotape, Betacam SP, dub, 0:08:05; koppel_01294 (Box 64)
      - Junk, 10/31/2001; Videotape, VHS, dub, 56:46:00; koppel_01295 (Box 56)
      - Leaving Home (Episode 7) (Archive) (Tape 1 of 2) (50M) (29-B), 11/13/2001; Videotape, Digital Betacam, dub, 1:00:00; koppel_01296 (Box 77)
      - Leaving Home (Episode 7) (Archive) (Tape 2 of 2) (50M) (29-B), 11/13/2001; Videotape, Digital Betacam, dub, 1:00:00; koppel_01297 (Box 77)
      - Leaving Home (LITH107 C2), 08/13/2002; Videotape, VHS, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01298 (Box 56)
      - Leaving Home (LITH107 C2), 08/13/2002; Videotape, VHS, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01299 (Box 56)
      - Leaving Home (LITH107 C2), 08/13/2002; Videotape, VHS, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01300 (Box 56)
      - Leaving Home (LITH107 C2), 08/13/2002; Videotape, VHS, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01301 (Box 56)
      - Leaving Home (LITH107 C2), 08/13/2002; Videotape, VHS, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01302 (Box 56)
      - Leaving Home (LITH107 C2), 08/13/2002; Videotape, VHS, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01303 (Box 56)
      - Leaving Home (LITH107 C2), 08/13/2002; Videotape, VHS, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01304 (Box 56)
      - Leaving Home (LITH107 C2), 08/13/2002; Videotape, VHS, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01305 (Box 56)
      - Milestones, 12/12/2001; Videotape, VHS, dub, 56:46:00; koppel_01310 (Box 57)
      - Milestones, 12/12/2001; Videotape, VHS, dub, 56:46:00; koppel_01311 (Box 57)
      - Milestones, 12/12/2001; Videotape, VHS, dub, 56:46:00; koppel_01312 (Box 57)
      - Money (LITH205 K1), 08/29/2002; Videotape, VHS, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01313 (Box 57)
      - Roots (LITH105 K2), 10/17/2001; Videotape, Betacam SP, dub, 56:46:00; koppel_01283 (Box 60)
      - Roots (LITH105 K1) (Edited Master) ("this is the old bad master"), 10/17/2001; Videotape, Digital Betacam, master, 56:46:00; koppel_01284 (Box 60)
      - Roots (LITH105 K2) (53B), 10/17/2001; Videotape, Digital Betacam, dub, 56:46:00; koppel_01285 (Box 60)
      - Roots (LITH105 K3) (Archive Reel 1 of 1), 06/05/2002; Videotape, Digital Betacam, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01286 (Box 61)
      - Roots (LITH105 K2), 10/17/2001; Videotape, VHS, dub, 56:46:00; koppel_01287 (Box 56)
      - Dub (Orig Air: 10/4/01), 01/30/2003; Videotape, Betacam, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01255 (Box 60)
      - Ripple Effect Clip Reel (Vietnam Clip Reel), 05/25/2001; Videotape, Betacam, dub, 0:37:00; koppel_01256 (Box 60)
      - The Ripple Effect (Fine Cut), 09/17/2001; Videotape, Betacam, dub, 0:24:26; koppel_01257 (Box 64)
      - Six Degrees of Separation (LITH101 C2), 08/14/2002; Videotape, VHS, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01258 (Box 56)
      - Six Degrees of Separation (LITH101 C2), 08/14/2002; Videotape, VHS, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01259 (Box 56)
      - Six Degrees of Separation (LITH101 C2), 08/14/2002; Videotape, VHS, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01260 (Box 56)
      - Six Degrees of Separation (LITH101 C2), 08/14/2002; Videotape, VHS, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01274 (Box 56)
      - Six Degrees of Separation (LITH101 C2), 08/14/2002; Videotape, VHS, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01275 (Box 56)
      - Six Degrees of Separation (LITH101 C2), 08/14/2002; Videotape, VHS, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01276 (Box 56)
      - Six Degrees of Separation (LITH101 C2), 08/14/2002; Videotape, VHS, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01277 (Box 56)
      - Six Degrees of Separation (LITH101 C2), 08/14/2002; Videotape, VHS, dub, 0:56:46; koppel_01278 (Box 56)
      - Voice, 10/12/2001; Videotape, Betacam SP, dub, 56:46:00; koppel_01281 (Box 60)
      - Blind Tom (Fine Cut), 09/17/2001; Videotape, Betacam, dub, 0:18:00; koppel_01282 (Box 64)
      - Highlights Reel (Rough Cut), 02/04/2002; Videotape, Betacam, master, 0:25:24; koppel_01314 (Box 64)
      - OPB/Nightline Docs (Rough Assemble): Milosevic rough/Bilboa and volcano, 2001; Videotape, Betacam, dub, 1:00:00; koppel_01315 (Box 77)
    - Life in Bold
      Early version of Life 360, a collaboration between Oregon Public Broadcasting and ABC News Nightline production staff. Holdings for this program are camera original studio footage.
      - Cam 4 (9:30 pre-tape), 03/13/2001; Videotape, Betacam, original footage, 1:00:00; koppel_01316 (Box 77)
      - Cam 4 (9:30 pre-tape), 03/13/2001; Videotape, Betacam, original footage, 1:00:00; koppel_01317 (Box 77)
      - Cam 5 (9:30 pre-tape), 03/13/2001; Videotape, Betacam, original footage, 1:00:00; koppel_01318 (Box 77)
      - Cam 5 (9:30 pre-tape), 03/13/2001; Videotape, Betacam, original footage, 1:00:00; koppel_01319 (Box 77)
      - Cam 6 (9:30 pre-tape), 03/13/2001; Videotape, Betacam, original footage, 1:00:00; koppel_01320 (Box 77)
      - Cam 6 (9:30 pre-tape), 03/13/2001; Videotape, Betacam, original footage, 1:00:00; koppel_01321 (Box 77)
      - Mix (9:30 pre-tape), 03/13/2001; Videotape, Betacam, original footage, 1:00:00; koppel_01322 (Box 77)
      - Cam 4 (Michel only) (2), 03/13/2001; Videotape, Betacam, original footage, 1:00:00; koppel_01323 (Box 77)
      - Cam 4 (Michel only) (2), 03/13/2001; Videotape, Betacam, original footage, 1:00:00; koppel_01324 (Box 77)
      - Cam 5 (Michel only) (2), 03/13/2001; Videotape, Betacam, original footage, 1:00:00; koppel_01325 (Box 77)
      - Cam 5 (Michel only) (2), 03/13/2001; Videotape, Betacam, original footage, 1:00:00; koppel_01326 (Box 77)
      - Cam 6 (Michel only) (2), 03/13/2001; Videotape, Betacam, original footage, 1:00:00; koppel_01327 (Box 61)
      - Cam 6 (Michel only) (2), 03/13/2001; Videotape, Betacam, original footage, 1:00:00; koppel_01328 (Box 61)
      - Mix No. 2 (Michel only) (2), 03/13/2001; Videotape, Betacam, original footage, 1:00:00; koppel_01329 (Box 61)
    - The Cronkite Report No. 9: Headlines and Sound Bites: Is That The Way It Is?, 03/22/1995; Videotape, VHS, dub, 1:00:00; koppel_02428 (Box 56)
    - Second Careers: David Graduation, Part 1 (David Parsons Graduation) (200), typed log inside tape case.; Videotape, Betacam, original footage, 1:30:00; koppel_02586 (Box 63)
    - Second Careers: Fontella Sermons (Earlier Sermon/Father's Day Sermon) (216), typed log inside tape case.; Videotape, Betacam, original footage, 1:30:00; koppel_02587 (Box 63)
    - Second Careers: Fontella Sermons (Father's Day Sermon cont.) (217), Videotape, Betacam, original footage, 1:30:00; koppel_02588 (Box 63)
    - Vote '88 (Cassette No. 18) (Air 23:00-24:00) (Bush Victory SOT No. 1) (DCTW 1837B), 11/08/1988; Bush's victory speech 23:51:30.; Videotape, 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic, dub, 1:00:00; koppel_02599 (Box 91)
    - Joia Jefferson: Resume Tape, 09/30/1988; Videotape, 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic SP, dub, 0:10:00; koppel_02600 (Box 91)
    - Profile Spot (30 sec.), 12/1988; Videotape, 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic, dub, 0:00:30; koppel_02601 (Box 91)
    - Boot Camp Dub (cut-down) (10), 11/05/1984; Videotape, 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic, dub, 0:05:36; koppel_02602 (Box 75)
    - Globe Presentation: Globe Pilot (Globe TV: A Ticket to the World), Videotape, VHS, dub, 0:05:00; koppel_02603 (Box 75)
    - Situational Leadership: The Background, Part I, Videotape, VHS, dub, 27:15:00; koppel_02605 (Box 75)
    - Situational Leadership: The Background, Part III, tape w/o case; Videotape, VHS, dub, 0:37:20; koppel_02606 (Box 75)
    - Babysitter WTVC ("cued to where hear faint cry") (Jan-38), Videotape, 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic SP, dub, 0:20:00; koppel_02607 (Box 75)
    - Wide Angle: China Courts [The People's Courts], [7/3/2007]; Xanadu Productions Ltd., Educational Broadcasting Corporation, and Independent Television Service (ITVS).; Videotape, VHS, dub, 1:00:00; koppel_02558 (Box 59)
    - [unidentified reel, possibly elements for Glaucoma piece], 1989?; from unlabeled original box, with misc. other tapes and Glaucoma.; Videotape, 1 inch videotape, master, 0:10:00; koppel_02473 (Box 229)
    - [unidentified reel, possibly elements for Glaucoma piece], 1989?; from unlabeled original box, with misc. other tapes and Glaucoma.; Videotape, 1 inch videotape, master, 0:10:00; koppel_02474 (Box 229)
  - Student radio broadcasts
    - House of Dreams, circa 1959; WAER radio, Syracuse University. Ted Koppel student work at Syracuse University. Radio drama narrated by Ted Koppel (with Irish brogue). "Frank Melton's hearse...." WAER student production. Begins mid-narrative; Digital audio file, dub, 0:17:05; belfer_015391
    - This is Moscow, circa 1959; WAER radio, Syracuse University. Ted Koppel student work, senior year at Syracuse University. Report on life in the Soviet Union, Soviet perceptions of the United States, etc. Compiled from tapes made during a two week stay in Moscow. Includes interviews with Ed Sullivan, Gov. Davis (North Dakota), Gov. McNichols (Colorado), Gov. Clyde (Utah), and various Russian citizens at the American Exhibition in Moscow; Digital audio file, dub, 0:57:04; belfer_015392
    - [Wendell "Windy" Craig - Allegro!], circa 1959; WAER radio, Syracuse University. Ted Koppel student work, Syracuse University. WAER classical music show "Allegro". Music with two short announcer breaks. Announcer identified as "Windy Craig" presumed to be Ted Koppel; Digital audio file, dub, 0:03:10; belfer_015393
    - [Koppel KZSU-1], 03/07/1961; KZSU radio, Stanford University. Ted Koppel student work. Mostly music (Bobby Vee, Frank Sinatra) with 1 brief announcer/disc jockey break. Announcer identified as "Marty", presumed to be Ted Koppel. Tuesday evening, March 7, Winter Quarter, 1961; Digital audio file, dub, 0:09:05; belfer_015394